Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 70, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: New Laws to Protect you in Your Job, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Notes: A Short Guide to the Labour Government: New Legislation on Workers at Work
  - Item 35: Tules and Standing Orders, 1982; Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: Hands Up for Democracy, 1983; Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Job Evaluation & Merit Rating, 1912; Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Box: 70, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Communications Employees and Good Service, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Curriculum: National Sales Training Seminar, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Sales Sparks, 1950; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 5 No. 5
  - Item 4: 1953 College Recruitment Program Report, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Careers in Western Union, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: A Modern Communications System Offering Career Opportunities
  - Item 6: A Window on the World, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Company Information Sheet for Western Union Telegraph Company, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Careers in Western Union, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: On the Move, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Equal Employement Opportunity Policy, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: The Word is Opportunity, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Join the Information Revolution, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Wanted: Girls, Women with Some Typing Ability, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Western Union Career Opportunities to Advance in Push-Button Communications and Electronics, 1957; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: A Message for High School Students, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Now You Can Have Steady, Interesting Employment with the World's Greatest Telegraph System, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: This is Western Union, 1952; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Annual Employment Report, 1953; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: 1962 Management Orientation Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Management Development Program Manual, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: 1957 Management Orientation Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Tuition Assistance Plan, 1974; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Your Benefits As A Management Employee, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Author: George P. Oslin
  - Item 25: Western Union Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Box: 70, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employment Manual, 1952; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: General Organization Outline and Charts, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1953 Orientation Program
  - Item 3: How Do We Rate?, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: Opinion Survey
  - Item 4: General Organization Outline & Charts, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Employee Relations Department, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: 1953 Management Orientation Program Report, 1957; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: 1953 Management Orientation Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Manual of Slary Administration For the Guidance of Supervisors, 1952; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Box: 70, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 1953 Westinghouse Diary and Employe Handbook, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Westinghouse Insurance Plan for Employes, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Westinghouse Personal Accident Insurance Plan Enrollment Form, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Westinghouse Long-Term Disability Benefit Plan Enrollment Form, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Long-Term Disability Benefit Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Personal Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Supplementary Group Life Insurance Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Long-Term Disability Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Personal Excess Liability Plan for Management Employes, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Supplementary Group Life Insurance Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: A Report from the Board of Advice to Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Westinghouse Pension Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Safety Rules for Electrical Maintenance and Construction Men, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Rules for Promoting Safety in Testing Operations, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Handbook for Salary Employes, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Safety Rules for the Safe Transportation of Loads by Cranes, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Television Radio Division Report to Employes, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: Employe Attitude Survey
  - Item 18: Rules and Safe Practices for Electrical Testing Operations, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: Switchgear and Large Rotating Apparatus
  - Item 19: Rules for Promoting Safety in Testing Operations, 1945; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: Electronic Equipment
  - Item 20: Welcome to Westinghouse, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Welcome to Westinghouse, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Employe Relations in Perspective, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Author: Howard S. Kalterborn
  - Item 23: Patent Agreement, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Westinghouse Forms, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Box: 70, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Program for Salaried Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: What's Cookin' in Safety, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Notes: N.S.C. Wood Products Newsletter
- Box: 70, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Box: 70, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Our Profit-Sharing Retirement Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: University of Wisconsin Instruction in Industrial Relations, 1956; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Graduate Degree Program in Industrial Relations University of Wisconsin, 1956; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Wisconsin Idea in Worers' Education, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Author: Robert Ozanne
    Notes: Reprint Series No. 18
  - Item 5: Industrial Research Organization, 1954; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Notes: The University of Wisconsin Engineering Institutes
  - Item 6: A Program for Economic Growth, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Notes: Center for the Study of Productivity Motivation
  - Item 7: The Industrial Management Institute Announces Supervisory Institutes (for Foremen and Supervisors), 1953; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: A Summary of A One Day Conference For Executive Management: Is Profit-Sharing The Answer?, 1952; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Notes: To Develop Better Business and Industrial Leaders
  - Item 9: The School for Workers, 1959; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Wisconsin State CIO Institute - 1953, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Your Educational Committee Can Get Moving Now!, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: You are Invited to Help Us Celebrate 50 Years of the Wisconsin Idea in Education, 1956; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: The University of Wisconsin Executive Leadership Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: The University of Wisconsin School for Workers, 1952; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Box: 70, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Medical Report, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Tests, 1952; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Box: 70, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Basic Retirement Plan For All Employees of Worcester Moulded Plastics Company, 1955; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Excess Retirement Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Box: 70, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Income, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Box: 70, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan for Employees and their Dependents, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Employee Savings and Profit Sharing Plan (as amended), 1953; Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    Notes: Trust Agreement Between The Rudolph Wulitzer Company, The Rudolph Wulitzer Companyof Pennsylvania; And The First National Bank of Chicago, As Trustee
- Box: 70, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Importance of Being Important Together, 1951; Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
    Author: Clarence A. Wimpfheimer
- Box: 70, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Classification and Compensation Plan for Positions in the Classified Service, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Merit Increase Report, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Box: 70, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Progress Sharing At American Motors, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 16)
    Author: I.B. Helburn
  - Item 2: A New Approach to Collective Bargaining? Progress Sharing At American Motors, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Box: 70, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Basic Supervision, Publication (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Telephone Institute Outline, Publication (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Box: 70, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Controller's Division Basic Training Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Box: 70, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Xerox Unit's Mission: Safety, Health, Clean Environment for Employees, Customers, Community, Publication (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Box: 70, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Case Study in Retraining, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 20)
    Author: Felician F. Foltman
    Notes: Management and Personnel Quarterly Vol. 1, No. 5, Autumn-Winter 1962
  - Item 2: Xerox Unveils Plans to Broaden Education Role, Publication (Box 70, Folder 20)
    Author: David J. Curtin
    Notes: For Immediate Release
- Box: 70, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Training Courses, 1908; Publication (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Box: 70, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Office, Library, and Laboratory Employment Policies in Yale University, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Summer Employment - Scholarship Assistance for Children of Faculty & Staff, 1972; Publication (Box 70, Folder 22)
    Author: Kimble M. Williams, Director of Personnel
    Notes: Inter-Office Correspondence
- Box: 70, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Purpose, Publication (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Box: 70, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Your Years at Yard-Man, Publication (Box 70, Folder 24)
    Notes: The Story of the Yard-Man Retirement Program
- Box: 70, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits For Designated Non-Exempt Salaried Employees of Youngstown, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Savings and Vacation Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Program of Insurance Benefits, 1971; Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Program of Insurance Benefits For Designated Exempt Salaried Employees of Youngstown, Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Savings and Vacation Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Program of Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Sales Training Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
- Box: 70, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: A Program of Group Insurance Consisting of Life Insurance, Death and Dismemberment Insurance and Sickness and Accident Benefits Prerpared fpr Employees of Zenith Radio Corporation, Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Medical Care Program for Employees of Zenith Radio Corporation, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Zenith Profit-Sharing Retirement Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Safety at the Factory, Office, Home, Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Wage Incentive Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Wage & Salary Administration Position Questionnaire I, Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Questions and Answers About The Zenith Profit-Sharing Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
- Box: 71, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Savings Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Training and Experience Requirements for Engineering and Scientific Positions, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Interdepartmental Communication, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Author: A.A. Flakoll
  - Item 4: Statement of Functions and Responsibilities, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Engineering & Scientific Job Families, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Engineering Cooperative Work-Study Program At Lockheed Missiles & Space Company, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Opportunities for Engineering/Scientific Students and Recetly Graduated Engineers/Scientists at Lockheed Missiles & Space Company, A Group Division of Lockheed Aircraft Corporation, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Engineering and Scientific Rate and Code List, Revision No. 21, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Author: E.J. Redmon
    Notes: Interdepartmental Communication
  - Item 9: LMSC E&S Nomograph, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Salary Range Structure, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Author: L.A. Mitchell
  - Item 11: Executive and Supervisory Occupational Code List, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Administrative Nomograph, 1962; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Lockheed Missiles & Space Company Administrative Job Families, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Administrative Rate and Code List, Revision No. 26, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Safety Regulations - Exempt Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Time Out for Fun in Colorful Santa Clara County, California, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Personal Safety is Everyone's Responsibility, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Notes: A Message to University Students, Staff and Faculty
  - Item 18: A Message to University Employees From Your security Department, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Free Collective Bargaining: What It Means to You!, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Notes: A Lockheed Aircraft Corporation Rerport to Employees Represented by the Machinists Union on the Thirtieth Anniversary of Its First Labor Contract with the Union
  - Item 20: Article VIII - Pay Rates, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Technical & Office Evaluation Plan: Hourly Jobs, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Notes: Lockheed-Georgia Company: A Division of Lockheed Aircraft Corporation
  - Item 22: Factory Restudy Evaluation Plan: Skill, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Wage Determination, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Manual of Functions and Responsibilities, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Organization Chart No. 15, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Management Directive, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Notes: Support of Employee Educational Programs
  - Item 27: Promotion Procedure, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Intercompany Transfers, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Special Certificate Plan: Professional/Technical Evening Program, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Employment Application, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Professional Employment Application, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: The Joint Lockheed-I.A.M. Income Security Program For Lockheed Employees represented by the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: The Joint Lockheed-I.A.M. Income Security Plan for Lockheed Employees represented by the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Notes: 12. Benefit plabs for Employee Security: Guaranteed Annual Wage or Supplementary Unemployment Compensation
  - Item 34: Basic Benefit Plan and Savings Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Evaluation Under Technical & Office Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: Employee Performance and Counseling Review, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Employee Performance & Counseling Review, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: Management Directive, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Notes: The "Open Door" Policy
  - Item 39: Employee Counseling, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: Hourly Promotion and Transfer, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 41: Grievance Form, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 42: Training Activity: Summary of 1967 Programs, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 43: Recruitment Methods, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 44: Testing, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 45: Statement of Facts & Issues, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Box: 71, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Lockheed Missiles & Space Company, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Author: T.E. Lyons
  - Item 2: New Worlds of Opportunity at Lockheed Missiles and Space Company, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Look at LockheedAs A Career, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Graduate Study Program for M.S. and Ph.D. Degrees in Science and Engineering
  - Item 4: Hourly Employee Performance Review, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Hourly Employee Performance Review, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Standard Practice Instructions, 1960; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: E.A.A. Evaluation Plan Report of Joint Committee Evaluation Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Management Policy Statement: Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: News Letter, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. VIII, No. 2
  - Item 10: Standard Practice Instructions: Settlement of Personnel Problems, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Factory Codes, Occupations and Rates: Alphabetical Index, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Office and Technical Codes, Occupations and Rates: Alphabetical Index: Labor Grades, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Salary Regulations, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Revisions: General
  - Item 14: Standard Practice InstructionsAdditional Compensation for Temporary Foreign Travel, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Standard Practice Instructions: Jury Duty, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Standard Practice Instructions: Reporting of Accidents, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Standard Practice Instructions: Physical Examinations, Medical Clearance of Employees, and Medical Limitation Control, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Standard Practice Instructions: Annual Physical Examinations - Executive and Management, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Salaried Employees Sick Leave planStandard Practice Instructions, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Standard Practice Instructions: Non-Exempt Employees' Sick Leave Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Standard Practice Instructions: Placement of LAI Personnel Returning from Overseas Assignments, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Standard Practice Instructions: Vacations for LAI Overseas Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Standard Practice Instructions: Exempt Employees' Sick Leave Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Standard Practice Instructions: Voluntary Termination or Dismissal of LAI Employees While on Overseas Assignment, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Standard Practice Instructions: Agreements of Employment or Letters of Assignment for LAI Overseas Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Standard Practice Instructions: Compensation for Extended Foreign Assignment, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: Standard Practice Instructions: Compensation from Extended Foreign Assignment, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Standard Practice Instructions: Compensation for Permanent Foreign Assingment, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Foreign Temporary Station Assignments - All Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: Standard Practive Instructions: Personnel Employment and Clear-In, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: Standard Practice Instructions: Notices of Commendation, Criticism, and Enforcement of Company Rules, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Corporate Management Memo to All Members of Supervosopm: Equal Employment Opportunity, 1961; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Author: Courtlandt S. Gross
  - Item 33: Corporate Management Memo To All Members of Supervision: Fifth Anniversary of the Lockheed Plan for Progress, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Permanent Station Assignment - Salaried Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: LAC/LAI Service Awards, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Standard Practice Instructions: Field Duty Assignments, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: Standard Practice Instructions: Training Programs, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: Lockheel Group of International Companies, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 39: Management Selection and Placement Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: Managerial Classification Program, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: The "Open Door" Policy, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: Domestic Temporary Station Assignments - Salaried Managerial Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 43: Description of Current Offerings: Seminars, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 44: Executive & Supervisory Mangerial Classifications (Alphabetical Listing), Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 45: Non-Supervisory Managerial Classifications (Alphabetical Listing), Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 46: Payment for Work in Excess of Normal Work Schedule for Salaried Managerial Personnel, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 47: Rotational Training Program, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 48: Supplement "C" Lockheed-Georgia Company and Aeronautical Machinists Local Lodge 709 Joint Statement of Policy for Application of Job Descriptions, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 49: Management Directive: Establishment and Reclassification of Occupations, 1957; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)